export const data=[
    {
        question: " React was invented by?",
        option1: "James Gosling",
        option2: "Guido Van Rossum",
        option3: "Jordon Walke",
        option4: "Graydon Hoare",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What does JSX stand for?",
        option1: "JavaScript XML",
        option2: "JavaScript Extension",
        option3: "Java Syntax Extension",
        option4: "Java XML Syntax",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is used for modular programming in Node.js?",
        option1: "Modules",
        option2: "Arrays",
        option3: "Objects",
        option4: "Loops",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following hooks is used for managing state in functional components?",
        option1: "useState",
        option2: "useEffect",
        option3: "useRef",
        option4: "useContext",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Which built-in method is used to parse incoming JSON requests?",
        option1: "JSON.read()",
        option2: "JSON.stringify()",
        option3: "JSON.parse()",
        option4: "JSON.convert()",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "How can you pass data from a parent component to a child component in React?",
        option1: "By using states",
        option2: "By using props",
        option3: "By using context",
        option4: "By using ref",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is the default data format used by MongoDB?",
        option1: "XML",
        option2: "BSON",
        option3: "CSV",
        option4: "JSON",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What does the fs module in Node.js provide?",
        option1: "File System operations",
        option2: " HTTP requests",
        option3: "Database management",
        option4: "Template engine support",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Which hook is used to perform side effects in functional components?",
        option1: "useState",
        option2: "useEffect",
        option3: "useRef",
        option4: "useReducer",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What type of database is MongoDB?",
        option1: "Relational",
        option2: "Key-Value",
        option3: "Document-oriented",
        option4: "Column-family",
        ans: 3,
    }

]